<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Material Login Example</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_dashboard">Dashboard</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tasker">TaskerActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_user_details">UserDetails</string>
    <string name = "before">
        . Have a good night’s sleep.\n
        . Eat well. Avoid fatty meals.\n
        . Drink plenty of fluids. Avoid alcohol and an excess of caffeine (tea, coffee).\n
        . Wear loose clothes (with sleeves that can be raised above the elbow).\n
        . Identify the “good veins” if you are a regular blood donor.
    </string>
    <string name = "whoCan">
        .Age: 18 to 65 years old. Above that, it comes down to the overall health status.\n
        .Weight: on average >60Kg for men, >50Kg for women. \n
        .If you are feeling well, and display no signs of infection. \n
        .You can give blood every 3 months, up to 4 times a year for women and 5 for men.\n
    </string>

    <string name = "happens">
        .You are required to present your ID card upon arrival.\n
        .You fill in a questionnaire and may be privately interrogated by a nurse.\n
        .Your hemoglobin level is checked to ensure you are not anemic. \n
        .Your temperature, blood pressure and pulse should be checked as well.
    </string>

    <string name = "benefits">
        .Detect medical conditions such as hypertension, anemia, blood-borne diseases, ongoing infections.\n
        .Reduce cancer risks, especially those related to blood (leukemia and lymphoma).Reduce cardiovascular events (heart attacks and strokes). \n
        .Replenish your blood by keeping the bone marrow active, regenerating red blood cells on a frequent basis.
    </string>

</resources>
